You all want a raise too
That's right
If we don't get a raise we'll quit
Yeah
No raise we leave
How much do you want
15,000
Do you all think so too
Lewes
We guys
work day and night to take care of
these frogs for you
You do nothing
and make 10 million just by reselling them
Giving us 15,000 a month
isn't too much to ask
Guys
Am I right
Exactly
Give us a raise
You really think you did all the work
Besides
the pay I give you
is already the highest in the industry
Others only pay 4,000
Walter's 10 million order
is due for delivery next month
We'll all leave if we don't get a raise
Let's see if you can
manage three greenhouses
by yourself
Yeah
No raise we leave
If you force us out
this order is ruined
Fine
You're all fired
Boss
Are you sure about this
That's a 10 million order
You're saving a few thousand on wages
at the cost of a 10 million order
That's my business
Now
please leave my farm
Guys he treats us like dirt
why should we stay
Anyway when he can't deliver
we won't be the ones losing money
Don't regret it Lewes
Even if you beg us on your knees
we won't come back
What did you say
Lewes' farm is going bankrupt
To save some wages
he fired all of us
From yesterday until now
his frogs haven't been fed at all
They'll all starve to death in two days
He signed a contract
If he can't deliver 50,000 frogs
next month
he'll have to pay 30 million in compensation
30 million
That's so much money
His previous earnings aren't
enough to cover it
I'd say Lewes got cocky
The big frog farmers in town
didn't even dare to take the order
yet he dared to take it as a beginner
Now look
he dug his own grave
Dear
Is Lewes really in trouble
Let's go
Let's go check on him